<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 12:01:45 -0230</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Photography</title>
      <link>/projects/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/photography/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I take pictures This project is about the pictures I take. Sometimes, they are pictures of cats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design</title>
      <link>/projects/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/design/</guid>
      <description>Working with a variety of clients designing websites, printed material, and identities. Being a freelance designer has been very rewarding and I’ve learned a ton about communication, budgeting, and managing expectations. Although tough to balance a full time job and freelancing on the side I enjoy the challenge. Freelancing has opened many doors and I’ve met many talented goal driven people. My favorite part of freelancing is seeing clients excited about their project and wanting to continue pushing for more great design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logo Design</title>
      <link>/projects/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/writing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Yourself</title>
      <link>/blog/love-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 12:01:45 -0230</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/love-yourself/</guid>
      <description>Aku gagal paham dengan yang masih keras kepala menjadikan militansi sebagai kompetisi. Apakah kita sengaja dibuat lupa bahwa kehidupan setiap orang pada dasarnya multidimensi sehingga arah, bentuk, dan strategi perlawanannya bukan hanya sekadar hitam dan putih? Mengapa kita justru malah terlena dalam narasi dikotomi semacam ini?
Mesianisme adalah mengapa kita gagal berkali-kali, karena energi dan kesadaran dialokasikan hanya pada yang itu-itu lagi, dengan cara yang itu-itu lagi; sedangkan abad terus berlari.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
